

Amrutha K Moily

My Contact

amruthamoily19@gmail.com

+919606673259

Hoige Jiddu House Post Kulai Hosabettu Mangalore - 575019

Soft Skill

- Quick Learner
- Collaboration / Teamwork
- Open-mindedness and adaptability
- Communication
- Critical thinking, creativity, and problem-solving
- · Multi-tasking
- Persistence and Patience
- Flexibility and Adaptability

Education Background

 Bachelor Of Engineering in Electronics and Communication Engineering

2016 - 2020 Sahyadri College of Engineering and Management.

CGPA: 7.3

Pre University Education

2014 - 2016 Govinda Dasa PU College, Surathkal Mangalore

Percentage: 86.5%

Secondary School

2011 - 2014

Vidyadayini High School, Surathkal Mangalore.

Percentage: 89.2%

About Me

Enthusiastic and creative team player with a strong background in planning, and maintenance of software programs, desirous of the role of Software Engineer at DC Inc. to hone my technical skills and expertise along with designing creative software and products as per the client's needs and enhance the reputation of your organization.

To incorporate working knowledge of customized software design and developer and coding along with honing my skills and contributing towards augmenting the company's reputation.

Professional Experience

Invenger Technologies Private Limited

Software Developer

Jun 2021 - Present

Technologies: Java 8, Angular 12, JUnit, Cypress, MySQL. Key responsibilities:

- Updating of Insupay Mobile Application base code as per the client's request.
- Updating the Base code for the Vendor payment portal as per a client requirement without affecting the functionality of the portal for other clients.
- Handling the maintenance task of payment Applications, wherein the task is to analyze the root cause and resolve the production issue
- Implement an Automated test-driven Environment for both Mobile Applications and web applications front-end and back-end, reducing the developer's Unit testing effort by 50%.

Prasanna Technologies Private Limited

Junior Process Associate

Oct 2020 - May 2021

Technologies: Java - 8, Regular Expressions, XML parsing Key responsibilities:

- Data extraction and formatting of Data.
- Led and trained a team of 12 Data Extraction Resources.
- Automated the process of data extraction by developing the JAVA tool.

Urjanet Energy Solution Private Limited

Software Engineer - Intern

Jan - Jul 2020

Technologies: Java Key responsibilities:

Extracting Data from the Utility Bills by using java driven tools

Achievements

- Organized an Aeromodelling workshop.
- Attended workshop on Python programming using Anaconda Software.
- Organized Aerophilia Notational Level Aero Modelling competition.

Technical Skill

- Operating System: Windows, Ubuntu.
- Technical Languages: Java, SQL, XML, HTML, JSON, Angular, C++, C.

• Software Tools:

- Eclipse
- Epsilon Editor
- Apachi Net Beans
- DB Browser SQlite
- My SQL
- Android Studio
- Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio
- IntelliJ IDEA
- SOAP UI.
- Atlasian Jira
- Amazon Web Service (AWS)
- Git Lab
- Jenkins

• Specific Skills:

- Java 8
- My SQL
- Database connectivity
- Regular Expressions
- Bulk File Processing
- Multithreading
- Servlets
- XML Parsing
- Code Obfuscation
- o Angular 12
- JUnit Unit Testing and Mockito
- Cypress automated Unit for Front-End
- Agile development environment

Projects

Web Applications

Company: Invenger Technologies Private Limited
Technologies: MySQL, Angular 12, Batch file processing,
Java 8, Cypress, JUnit, IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Studio Code,
Apache Tomcat, Wild fly, Jira, Jenkins.

Project name: Util Application

- Uploading a file to bank sftp using the batch file commands.
- Conversion of .pem private key to .ppk format using the batch file command

Project name: Customer Portal, Vendor Portal

- Worked on Client specific Product updating process
- Worked both on Front-end Angular framework and Java back-end service.
- Worked on developing both front-end and back-end automated test cases which reduced the efforts required for testing and improved software quality.

Project name: Payment Web service

- Back-end service to perform all payment-related operations in any of the organization's applications mentioned above.
- worked in identifying the deadlock that occurred in the application.

Insure Pay Mobile App Development

Company: Invenger Technologies Private Limited Technologies: AWS, SQLcipher, Android Studio, GitHub, Putty, Mockito, Jira, Jenkins.

- Handling session Invalidation of Insurpay app
- Code Obfuscation, for Android.
- solved PCI compliance gaps.
- WSS security header to prevent replay attack.
- configured the layout based on different clients' needs in the same base code.
- Added Espresso and JUnit test Driven Environment for the InsurePay app.

Process Automation in E-Publication

Company: Prasanna Technologies Private Limited Technologies: Java, Bulk File processing, Multithreading, RegEx, Xpath parsing, XML Expression

• Pattern recognition

validator.

- XPath to structure and arrive well-formed XML document
- Huge File Processing with multithreading.
- Reduced the Efforts by 50%.
- Working with Scripting Languages like JavaScript, and XMI
- Validating against pre-conditions and generating automated logs.

E-Publication core Operations

Company: Prasanna Technologies Private Limited Tools and Technologies used: Epsilon Editor, XML, Oxygen XML Editor.

- Conversion Processes Like Reference Tagging, Citation Tagging, and Graphics Tags to Source Files.
- Validating the XML File for Tagging and Related Issues Using the Oxygen Editor.
- Quality checks final digital products to ensure ASCD's high-quality standard.

Data Extraction from Utility Bills

Company: Urjanet Energy Solutions Private Limited
Tools and Technologies: Eclipse Editor, XPath,
RegularExpressions, Java, Data Extraction, Jira, Jenkins.

- Extracting data from Utility Bills using Java Application.
- The data is extracted from websites using XPath.
- Data is Extracted and Modified.
- Data in the table is Extracted Using the SQLite query.